Ted Koppel Collection
Ted Koppel Collection
- Nightline, 1980-2005
  - 1981
    - Nightline: Drunk Driving, 12/30/1981; koppel_nl81123001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
  - 1982
    - Nightline: Political Humor, 01/01/1982; koppel_nl82010101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: A New National Security Advisor, 01/04/1982; koppel_nl82010401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Auto Industry: Doomsday Ahead?, 01/05/1982; koppel_nl82010501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Corporate Takeovers, 01/06/1982; koppel_nl82010601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: New Evidence on the Plot to Kill the Pope, 01/07/1982; koppel_nl82010701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Neonatal Care, 01/08/1982; koppel_nl82010801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Cold Wave of the Century, 01/11/1982; koppel_nl82011101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Red Brigades: New Target - America, 01/12/1982; koppel_nl82011201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Disaster on the Potomac, 01/13/1982; koppel_nl82011301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Investigating the Crash, 01/14/1982; koppel_nl82011401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Bob Jones University, 01/15/1982; koppel_nl82011501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Cockpit Voice and Flight Data Recorders, 01/18/1982; koppel_nl82011801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Amerasians: Children Without a Country, 01/19/1982; koppel_nl82011901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Guarding Against Terrorism, 01/20/1982; koppel_nl82012001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Super Bowl: A Sacred American Holiday, 01/22/1982; koppel_nl82012201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: N.Y. Nuclear Mishap: National Impact?, 01/25/1982; koppel_nl82012501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Reagan Vision: New Federalism, New Spirit, 01/26/1982; koppel_nl82012601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Soviet Psychiatry: A Political Tool, 01/27/1982; koppel_nl82012701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: The Dozier Rescue, 01/28/1982; koppel_nl82012801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: FDR: Anecdotes and Memories, 01/29/1982; koppel_nl82012901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Right to Bear Arms?, 02/01/1982; koppel_nl82020101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: Neonatal Care Decisions, 02/02/1982; koppel_nl82020201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 106)
    - Nightline: El Salvador: The Decisive Battle?, 02/03/1982; koppel_nl82020301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: The JFK Tapes, 02/04/1982; koppel_nl82020401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Gambling: A National Obsession, 02/05/1982; koppel_nl82020501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Reagan Misstatements, 02/08/1982; koppel_nl82020801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Teen Birth Control: Should Parents Know?, 02/09/1982; koppel_nl82020901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Chemical Weapons: A New U.S. Initiative, 02/10/1982; koppel_nl82021001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Human Rights: Politics vs. Morality, 02/11/1982; koppel_nl82021101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Psychology on the Airwaves, 02/12/1982; koppel_nl82021201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Auto Worker Concessions, 02/15/1982; koppel_nl82021501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: The U.S. and the U.N., 02/16/1982; koppel_nl82021601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Toughlove for Teens in Trouble, 02/17/1982; koppel_nl82021701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: U.S. Covert Activities, 02/18/1982; koppel_nl82021801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Physical Fitness, 02/19/1982; koppel_nl82021901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Smoking and Cancer: The New Report, 02/22/1982; koppel_nl82022201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Voting Rights: The Burke County Case, 02/23/1982; koppel_nl82022301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: El Salvador: Five Perspectives, 02/24/1982; koppel_nl82022401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Political Action Committees, 02/25/1982; koppel_nl82022501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Video Game Parlors, 02/26/1982; koppel_nl82022601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: The Atlanta Murders: Case Solved?, 03/01/1982; koppel_nl82030101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: U.S. and China: Ten Years After Shanghai, 03/02/1982; koppel_nl82030201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Reagan Administration Strains and Stresses, 03/03/1982; koppel_nl82030301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: TV Boycott: Censorship or Responsibility?, 03/04/1982; koppel_nl82030401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: John Belushi: His Life, Death and Career, 03/05/1982; koppel_nl82030501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Sexual Harassment on the Job, 03/08/1982; koppel_nl82030801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Jupiter Effect and Doomsday Hysteria, 03/09/1982; koppel_nl82030901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Nuclear Freeze Movement, 03/10/1982; koppel_nl82031001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: The Resignation of Harrison Williams, 03/11/1982; koppel_nl82031101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Drugs and the Entertainment Business [PART 1], 03/12/1982; koppel_nl82031201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Drugs and the Entertainment Business [PART 2], 03/12/1982; koppel_nl82031202; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Secrecy for Secret Agents, 03/15/1982; koppel_nl82031501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Yasir Arafat on Lebanon and the PLO, 03/16/1982; koppel_nl82031601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Moshe Arens and the View from Israel, 03/17/1982; koppel_nl82031701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 107)
    - Nightline: Fort Wayne Floods, 03/18/1982; koppel_nl82031801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Cameras in the Courtroom, 03/19/1982; koppel_nl82031901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: The Future in Outer Space, 03/22/1982; koppel_nl82032201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Guatemalan Coup and West Bank Unrest, 03/23/1982; koppel_nl82032301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: U.S. and Japan: A Commercial Rivalry, 03/24/1982; koppel_nl82032401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: U.S.-Nicaragua Crossroads, 03/25/1982; koppel_nl82032501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Death Lists and Deadlines: Media in Salvador, 03/26/1982; koppel_nl82032601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: El Salvador Elections, 03/29/1982; koppel_nl82032901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Hinckley Case and American Justice, 03/30/1982; koppel_nl82033001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Nuclear Weapons Debate, 03/31/1982; koppel_nl82033101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Hospital Trauma Units, 04/01/1982; koppel_nl82040101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Argentina, Britain and the Falkland Islands, 04/02/1982; koppel_nl82040201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Britain: Anchors Aweigh, 04/05/1982; koppel_nl82040501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: The Great Spring Blizzard of 1982, 04/06/1982; koppel_nl82040601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Falklands: The Crisis Deepens, 04/07/1982; koppel_nl82040701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: U.S. Role in the Falkland Negotiations, 04/08/1982; koppel_nl82040801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Falklands: Argentina's Gamble, 04/09/1982; koppel_nl82040901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Argentine Terms for Falkland Withdrawal, 04/12/1982; koppel_nl82041201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: The U.S. Tilts to Britain, 04/13/1982; koppel_nl82041301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Palestinian Nationalism and Israeli Security, 04/14/1982; koppel_nl82041401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Britain and Argentina: The Financial War, 04/15/1982; koppel_nl82041501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Urban Squatters, 04/16/1982; koppel_nl82041601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: U.S. Navy Buildup, 04/19/1982; koppel_nl82041901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: What Next in the Falklands?, 04/20/1982; koppel_nl82042001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Israeli Raid: Warning or Provocation?, 04/21/1982; koppel_nl82042101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Nuclear Weapons: What to Do About Them, 04/22/1982; koppel_nl82042201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: War Alert in the Falklands, 04/23/1982; koppel_nl82042301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Jimmy Carter on the Middle East, 04/26/1982; koppel_nl82042601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: War or Peace in the Falklands?, 04/27/1982; koppel_nl82042701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Battle of the Budget, 04/29/1982; koppel_nl82042901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: Backing the British: The U.S. Decision, 04/30/1982; koppel_nl82043001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 108)
    - Nightline: War Reporting: What's Withheld and Why, 05/03/1982; koppel_nl82050301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Falkland War and Western Solidarity, 05/04/1982; koppel_nl82050401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Falkland Peace Proposals, 05/05/1982; koppel_nl82050501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Prayer in Public Schools, 05/06/1982; koppel_nl82050601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Naval Strategy and New Technology of War, 05/07/1982; koppel_nl82050701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: An Argentine Concession?, 05/10/1982; koppel_nl82051001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Plight of the American Farmer, 05/11/1982; koppel_nl82051101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Britain and Argentina: The War on the Press [PART 1], 05/12/1982; koppel_nl82051201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Britain and Argentina: The War on The Press [PART 2], 05/12/1982; koppel_nl82051202; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Television Diplomacy, 05/13/1982; koppel_nl82051301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Back Pain, 05/14/1982; koppel_nl82051401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Divided Families: East and West, 05/17/1982; koppel_nl82051701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: British Proposals: Argentine Reply, 05/18/1982; koppel_nl82051801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Falklands: Bracing for War, 05/19/1982; koppel_nl82051901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Falklands: Is All-Out War Inevitable?, 05/20/1982; koppel_nl82052001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: British Invasion, 05/21/1982; koppel_nl82052101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Falklands Future if Britain Wins, 05/24/1982; koppel_nl82052401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Argentine Independence Day, 05/25/1982; koppel_nl82052501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Cosia Mendez: Argentina's View, 05/26/1982; koppel_nl82052601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Argentina's Week of the Missing, 05/27/1982; koppel_nl82052701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: The Pope Visits England, 05/28/1982; koppel_nl82052801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: British Victory: A Matter of Days?, 05/31/1982; koppel_nl82053101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Reagan to Europe: The Making of a Tour, 06/01/1982; koppel_nl82060101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Margaret Thatcher's Moral Crusade, 06/02/1982; koppel_nl82060201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Galtieri: A Time for Firmness, 06/03/1982; koppel_nl82060301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Mideast Flare-up, 06/04/1982; koppel_nl82060401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Israel in Lebanon/Kirkpatrick and the U.N., 06/07/1982; koppel_nl82060701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Wider War in the Middle East?, 06/08/1982; koppel_nl82060801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Israeli Aim: A New Political Reality?, 06/09/1982; koppel_nl82060901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Lebanon: The Fighting Continues, 06/10/1982; koppel_nl82061001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Ceasefire in Lebanon, 06/11/1982; koppel_nl82061101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Argentine (Virtual) Surrender, 06/14/1982; koppel_nl82061401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 109)
    - Nightline: Lebanon and Falklands: U.S. Gains and Losses, 06/15/1982; koppel_nl82061501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Falkland Costs, 06/16/1982; koppel_nl82061601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Woodward and Bernstein: Watergate, 06/17/1982; koppel_nl82061701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Lebanon: The Toll in Human Suffering, 06/18/1982; koppel_nl82061801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Hinckley: Insane, 06/21/1982; koppel_nl82062101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Insanity Plea on Trial, 06/22/1982; koppel_nl82062201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Schizophrenia, 06/23/1982; koppel_nl82062301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Has Israel Gone Too Far?, 06/24/1982; koppel_nl82062401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Haig Steps Down, 06/25/1982; koppel_nl82062501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: The Donovan Case, 06/28/1982; koppel_nl82062801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Civil Defense: Surviving a Nuclear War, 06/29/1982; koppel_nl82062901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Personnel Troubles: Reagan Hotspot, 06/30/1982; koppel_nl82063001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Scandal on Capitol Hill, 07/01/1982; koppel_nl82070101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: End of the ERA, 07/02/1982; koppel_nl82070201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Sports and Politics, 07/05/1982; koppel_nl82070501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Should We Send Marines to Lebanon?, 07/06/1982; koppel_nl82070601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Beirut Negotiations Sunday Deadline?, 07/07/1982; koppel_nl82070701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Soviet Warning/PLO Evacuation Talks, 07/08/1982; koppel_nl82070801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: The Crash of Flight 759, 07/09/1982; koppel_nl82070901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Falkland Lessons: British Examination, 07/12/1982; koppel_nl82071201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Shultz and Bechtel, 07/13/1982; koppel_nl82071301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Iran Invades Iraq, 07/14/1982; koppel_nl82071401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Vietnam Veterans, 07/15/1982; koppel_nl82071501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Jail for Sun Myung Moon?, 07/16/1982; koppel_nl82071601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Florida Deer Kill/Animal Research, 07/19/1982; koppel_nl82071901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: PLO Future: Saudi-Syrian Plan, 07/20/1982; koppel_nl82072001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: IRA Bombings, 07/21/1982; koppel_nl82072101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Watt Offshore Drilling Plan, 07/22/1982; koppel_nl82072201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: The Haitian Problem, 07/23/1982; koppel_nl82072301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Will the PLO Recognize Israel?, 07/26/1982; koppel_nl82072601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: El Salvador: Human Rights and U.S. Aid, 07/27/1982; koppel_nl82072701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Doing Business with Moscow, 07/28/1982; koppel_nl82072801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 110)
    - Nightline: Israel and U.S. Public Support, 07/29/1982; koppel_nl82072901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: The Business of Marijuana, 07/30/1982; koppel_nl82073001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Unresolved Conflicts in the Falkland Islands, 08/02/1982; koppel_nl82080201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: U.S. Relations with India, 08/03/1982; koppel_nl82080301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: American Pressure on Israel, 08/04/1982; koppel_nl82080401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Oraflex and Arthritis, 08/05/1982; koppel_nl82080501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Hollywood Superstars, 08/06/1982; koppel_nl82080601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: The War in Lebanon, 08/09/1982; koppel_nl82080901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: The Death Penalty, 08/10/1982; koppel_nl82081001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Air Safety: Wind Shear, 08/11/1982; koppel_nl82081101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Henry Fonda, 08/13/1982; koppel_nl82081301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Reagan Tax Hike: Conservative Skirmish, 08/16/1982; koppel_nl82081601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Stock Market Rally, 08/17/1982; koppel_nl82081701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Glen Cove and the Russians, 08/18/1982; koppel_nl82081801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Kissinger: Middle East Future, 08/19/1982; koppel_nl82081901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Lebanon: Evacuation Begins, 08/20/1982; koppel_nl82082001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Mideast in Transition, 08/23/1982; koppel_nl82082301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Wall Street Surge: Worldwide Recovery?, 08/24/1982; koppel_nl82082401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Marines in Lebanon, 08/25/1982; koppel_nl82082501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Draft Non-Registration, 08/26/1982; koppel_nl82082601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: U.S. Pipeline Sanctions, 08/27/1982; koppel_nl82082701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Drug Smuggling, 08/30/1982; koppel_nl82083001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Solidarity Anniversary, 08/31/1982; koppel_nl82083101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Reagan Mideast Initiative, 09/01/1982; koppel_nl82090101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Mexican Financial Crisis, 09/02/1982; koppel_nl82090201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Us Festival: High Technology, High Times, 09/03/1982; koppel_nl82090301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Robot Revolution, 09/06/1982; koppel_nl82090601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Nixon in Peking, 09/07/1982; koppel_nl82090701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Merchants of Death (Gov't Arms Sales), 09/08/1982; koppel_nl82090801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Conestoga 1: Dawn of a New Space Era?, 09/09/1982; koppel_nl82090901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Miss America Pageant, 09/10/1982; koppel_nl82091001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Pro Football Strike?, 09/13/1982; koppel_nl82091301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 111)
    - Nightline: Bashir Gemayel, Princess Grace [PART 1], 09/14/1982; koppel_nl82091401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Bashir Gemayel, Princess Grace [PART 2], 09/14/1982; koppel_nl82091402; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Arafat in Rome/Israel in Beirut, 09/15/1982; koppel_nl82091501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: The Rise and Fall of Sadegh Ghotbzadeh, 09/16/1982; koppel_nl82091601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Abortion Clinic Violence, 09/17/1982; koppel_nl82091701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Massacre Aftermath, 09/20/1982; koppel_nl82092001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Massacre: Is Israel Responsible?, 09/21/1982; koppel_nl82092101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Ferdinand Marcos: Patriot or Tyrant?, 09/22/1982; koppel_nl82092201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Cambodian Refugees: The Forgotten People, 09/23/1982; koppel_nl82092301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Herpes, 09/24/1982; koppel_nl82092401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: MIAs: The Search Continues, 09/27/1982; koppel_nl82092701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Marines: A Long Stay in Lebanon?, 09/28/1982; koppel_nl82092801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Gay Power: The New Political Activism, 09/29/1982; koppel_nl82092901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Alexander Haig Reflects, 09/30/1982; koppel_nl82093001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: The Ascent of Mount Everest, 10/01/1982; koppel_nl82100101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: US-USSR: 25 Years of Space Exploration, 10/04/1982; koppel_nl82100401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: The Tylenol Scare, 10/05/1982; koppel_nl82100501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: PCBs: Chemical Poison, National Problem, 10/06/1982; koppel_nl82100601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Amerasian Children, 10/07/1982; koppel_nl82100701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Coping with Unemployment, 10/08/1982; koppel_nl82100801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Swedish Submarine Search, 10/11/1982; koppel_nl82101101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Communist Poland and the Catholic Church, 10/12/1982; koppel_nl82101201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Reagan Message: Stay the Course, 10/13/1982; koppel_nl82101301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Vietnam Veterans Memorial, 10/14/1982; koppel_nl82101401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Demystifying Wall Street, 10/15/1982; koppel_nl82101501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: NFL Talks: Behind Closed Doors, 10/18/1982; koppel_nl82101801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Boeing and Airbus: The War to Win the Skies, 10/20/1982; koppel_nl82102001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Nuclear Fallout: Did the Government Lie?, 10/21/1982; koppel_nl82102101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Cuban Missile Crisis, 10/22/1982; koppel_nl82102201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: John DeLorean and the Stainless Steel Dream, 10/25/1982; koppel_nl82102501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: British Spy Leak, 10/26/1982; koppel_nl82102601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Unrest in Israel, 10/27/1982; koppel_nl82102701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 112)
    - Nightline: Nuclear Freeze: A Debate, 10/28/1982; koppel_nl82102801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 113)
    - Nightline: Halloween '82: A Scare Story, 10/29/1982; koppel_nl82102901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 113)
    - Nightline: Handgun Registration: Proposition 15, 11/01/1982; koppel_nl82110101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 113)
    - Nightline: Is There Life After (Political) Death?, 11/03/1982; koppel_nl82110301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 113)
    - Nightline: Teen Contraception: Baltimore Experiment, 11/04/1982; koppel_nl82110401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 113)
    - Nightline: The Dartmouth Review, 11/05/1982; koppel_nl82110501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 113)